<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Geekycat Blog</title>
    <link>https://blog.geekycat.in/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Geekycat Blog</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:12:33 +0530</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://blog.geekycat.in/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>XSS using postMessage in Google Cloud Theia notebooks [Google VRP]</title>
      <link>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/xss-using-postmessage-in-google-cloud-theia-notebooks/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Jan 2023 20:12:33 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/xss-using-postmessage-in-google-cloud-theia-notebooks/</guid>
      
      <description>This write-up is a part of a series of write-ups about the bugs I and Sivanesh found in Google Cloud in 2022.
While exploring Google Cloud’s Vertex AI Workbench, we noticed that we could create a workbench with Theia. Theia is the IDE that Google also uses in Cloud Shell. From reading previous research, we know that Theia implementations could be problematic.
After deploying a Theia instance workbench, I noticed that the version was not the latest.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Client-Side SSRF to Google Cloud Project Takeover [Google VRP]</title>
      <link>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/client-side-ssrf-to-google-cloud-project-takeover/</link>
      <pubDate>Thu, 12 Jan 2023 19:42:44 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/client-side-ssrf-to-google-cloud-project-takeover/</guid>
      
      <description>This write-up is a part of a series of write-ups about the bugs I and Sivanesh found in Google Cloud in 2022.
Google Cloud offers Vertex AI, which lets you build, deploy and scale machine learning models. In addition to various other features, Vertex AI also provides a &amp;ldquo;Workbench&amp;rdquo; feature. Workbench enables you to create Jupyter notebook-based development environment on the cloud. If you have used a Jupyter notebook, you would know that there are a lot of things that could go wrong here.</description>
      
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>[Google VRP] Hijacking Google Docs Screenshots</title>
      <link>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/hijacking-google-docs-screenshots/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 27 Dec 2020 19:13:19 +0530</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://blog.geekycat.in/posts/hijacking-google-docs-screenshots/</guid>
      
      <description>Brief: I was able to hijack Google Docs screenshot of any document exploiting postmessage misconfiguration and a browser behavior.
Google have a feature called &amp;ldquo;Send Feedback&amp;rdquo; in most of their product. As the name suggests it helps Google to get feedback from users when they face some issue. The feature have an options to add screenshots with a brief description about the issue.
As this is a common feature available in most of their sites, they have deployed the functionality in https://www.</description>
      
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
